# **Mark Franscot**

## **Elementary School Teacher**

Whittier, CA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Mark-Franscot/e4f8dc15f662e7a7

I have been a classroom teacher in grades kindergarten through sixth for 25 years. I have experience as a literacy coach, a grade level facilitator, and an intervention teacher. I have several years of experience in special education as well.

I appreciate your consideration for employment.

Mark Franscot

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Elementary School Substitute Teacher**

Little Lake City School District - Santa Fe Springs, CA -

October 2014 to Present

### **Elementary School Teacher**

Los Angeles Unified School District - Los Angeles, CA -

June 1989 to June 2014

#### **EDUCATION**

### Bachelor's in Child Psychology/Development

Cal State Los Angeles - Los Angeles, CA

**SKILLS** 

Literacy Coach - 2 years, Grade Level Facilitator, and Intervention Teacher.

MILITARY SERVICE

Service Country: US

Branch: Air Force

Rank: Senior Airman E-3

July 1984 to June 1989

I provided administrative support for NATO allied forces in Europe in the planning and implementation of war excercises at Ramstien Air Base, Germany.

Commendations:

6 service ribbons

## CERTIFICATIONS/LICENSES

# **BCLAD** in Spanish

Multiple Subject Teaching Credential (valid: 2020)